Try me!

Contact

phone +31622040319
email info@arejo.nl
location The Hague,
Netherlands
github github
portfolio portfolio
linkedin LinkedIn

About me

Startup founder turned developer.

Extremely passionate about building beautiful, practical and smart things. Selfstarting, highly determined, obsessively persistent.

Having completed the Frontend section of the Full-Stack Career Course on codecademy, I am eager to practice my new found skills as a Front-end / React Developer.

Open for a junior position or Freelance assignment. Remote / hybrid preferred. Get in touch!

Experience

2021 - Current Arejas The Hague

2019/2022 Arejas The Hague

2010-2019 privately held

2016-2017 Camptoo.nl The Hague

2015-2016 Yippie.nl Amsterdam

2011-2014 OWNR The Hague

Becoming a Full-Stack JavaScript Developer

Bootcamp on Codecademy, Studying React / Express. Build and sold a campervan to be able to study fulltime. See: Education / About me.

Freelance Developer

Wordpress websites & webshops for different clients using Divi, Elementor, WooCommerce, HTML and CSS.

mijnJohan.nl

Development, Marketing and Sales. Homegrown accountancy software for independent entrepreneurs. Passive Income Company.

Growth Hacker

Head responsible for the growth of the product-offering for this peer-2-peer Campers & Caravans renting platform, using the complete online marketing spectrum including Goal Tracking, Analytics, Split Testing and Conversion Optimisation.

First marketing Officer

Head responsible for the first growth spurt in users of this shopping-app, using the complete online marketing spectrum including Facebook Ads, Google Ads, Goal Tracking, Analytics, Split Testing and Conversion Optimisation.

Startup Founder

Internet startup in action sports. Responsible for marketing, sales, investors, product-development and allround succes. Collaborations with among others: Quiksilver / DC shoes and Nitro Snowboards.

Key Skills

Building web-apps from start to finish Rocking React & Redux

Tech Skills

HTML
CSS
JavaScript
React
Redux
Node.js
Express.js
SQL
Git
GitHub
TDD
Mocha
JEST
React Testing Library
JSON

Education

2021 - Present

2020 - 2021

codecademy

2008-2010 WdKa Rotterdam

1998-2004 Ashram College Alphen aan den Rijn

Full-Stack Developer Career Path Course

Becoming a Full-Stack web developer learning to build web-apps' front-end and back-end using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Redux, Node, Express, SQL, TDD, Mocha, Jest, React Testing Library, Markdown, JSON, Git & Github.

Build a back-end app with JavaScript

A predecessor to codecademy's back-end engineer career path. This was my introduction to JavaScript, Node, Express, SQL and building API's.

Creative Advertising

Art Direction, concepting $\&\ realisation.$ Arts Academy of Rotterdam.

Atheneum

Atheneum. Focus on Economics & Society. Field of choice: Computer Science. Research paper: Encryption.

Marketing Skills

Google Analytics
Goal Tracking
Growth Hacking Principles
Split Testing
Conversion Optimalisation
Google Adwords
Facebook Ads

Additional Skills

Adobe Creative Suite Google Sketchup SCRUM Agile

Certifications

• Back-end app with Javascript | Write API's with Node, Express & SQL | Codecademy | Jan '21

Languages

Dutch English German Spanish

Hobbie

Snowboarding Skateboarding Surfing Wakeboarding Climbing Guitar Travel Campervans